no i just uh recently uh went back to
college
finished my degree thank you
thank you i went
got my degree in philosophy
applause isn't necessary response
well seriously i have a philosophy
degree so now now i am
i'm a stand-up comedian an actor
and a philosopher so i have i have three
ways of not making money
very good it was interesting taking
philosophy i don't know if anybody's
ever taking a philosophy class but
one of my first classes i get in there
i'm sitting in there
and professor walks in he goes
the very first thing you need to
understand
about philosophy is that there
are no absolute truths in the universe
i'm sitting there just like you guys are
probably sitting here thinking wow
the tests in this class are going to be
easy
i started thinking i was like hey
he's like yes um
yeah um well if
okay okay if there are no um absolute
truths
in the universe would not the statement
that there are no absolute truths
be an absolute truth thus negating the
idea that there are no absolute truths
why don't we just go ahead and play
[Music]
hangman
we had one class where all we talked
about
was chairs
and then and then we get into the
there's
like friday you know we're on there and
and the teacher is like okay we're going
to have a quiz
all right in this quiz you are to defend
your own existence
what i'm sitting there thinking you know
maybe it's not too late to go get a real
degree like history or english
so i just i was like the heck with this
i'm going so i just got up
and i started leaving and the teacher's
like excuse me
yeah where are you going
who are you talking to
i'll take the a i'm always a little
nervous about that joke because
sometimes people just stare at me like
the entire state of wyoming
just stared at
he's probably from wyoming
local man robs wendy's with alligator
we're the alligator boys now
mom mom
[Music]